[theme music playing]
[tense music playing]
[screaming]
[shattering sound]
[reporter] Diego Torillo has the lead
over Congressman Julio Ardiente
in the election.
[people shouting]
The Ardientes always win.
Julio Ardiente's winning.
-Huh?
-What?
[Emilia screams]
You're going to have us killed, huh?
In your dreams!
[Julio] My grandson, victory is yours.
-Tell me who should pay.
-[Arnaldo groans]
[Ivy] How long will he stay like this?
It might take him months
before he can fully recover
and regain all his memory back.
[Ivy] Governor Julio Ardiente,
congratulations.
Your new title suits you.
[Julio] My enemies should start
saying their prayers
because this is
the beginning of their end.
[Diego] So Julio Ardiente, I am
challenging you to a recount,
to find out who the people
of this province voted for!
[crowd chanting]
Julio Ardiente is a cheater!
[Ivy] Tell your men to stop this!
[Julio] Who are you to give me orders?
No one tells me what to do.
You need me more than I need you!
[Emilia] An Ardiente never loses.
I will always be an Ardiente.
I will rise up and destroy you all.
[Julio] Cheers!
Thank you very much for your support.
[woman] Congratulations.
Thank you very much.
[Ivy] Your actions make
my skin crawl, Julio.
I know you were just testing me.
[indistinct chatter]
But the next time you do it,
I'll make sure you'll regret it.
[tense music plays]
[indistinct chatter]
Thank you, everyone.
[Fernan] Diego.
Julio's men raided our homes…
-and stole all our belongings.
-[somber music playing]
Mister Fernan, we'll get back
what they stole.
Don't worry.
Mister Danny, are you okay?
-Yeah.
-Does it hurt?
-It does.
-Diego.
-Nanny. Uncle.
-Julio's men tried to…
…run us over while we were marching.
What?
Were you hurt?
Your uncle Pandoy and I are fine,
but there were some people who got hurt.
-Where are they?
-They're in the hospital.
But thankfully, no one died.
We'll look for help.
-Yes.
-We'll look for help.
Don't worry.
That old man really has no mercy.
-Nanny.
-He has no conscience!
That's enough. We'll look for help.
Ana, where's Diego?
-Jepoy.
-Diego.
Divine Oytengco and Miss Cora are dead.
Only Julio would do something like that.
Now, Emilia's case
is going to be dismissed.
What?!
Jepoy, that's impossible.
They're under the
witness protection program.
There are people guarding them.
Yes, Ms. Camia, that's what we know.
But they're dead.
[Camia gasps]
[somber music intensifies]
Diego.
I'm speaking to you as a friend.
We can't take the Ardientes
down just by protesting.
Your signs are useless
against their bullets.
Now's the time.
We have to fight them.
We have to arm ourselves.
We have to fight back!
No. Violence isn't the answer to evil.
[tense music playing]
Do you even hear yourself?
They'll kill you all
if you don't fight back.
-You have to fight back!
-We are fighting back.
We're fighting back in the right way!
Tell me, what is the right thing to do?!
What good thing
has ever happened in Ardiente?!
Come on! Tell me!
Our witnesses are dead.
People are getting hurt, Diego!
-What's the right thing to do?!
-Jepoy!
That's enough.
We use guns to protect ourselves…
-…not to kill people!
-Unbelievable!
[Anna] Jepoy!
You think you're an angel.
But this town isn't a
place for angels, Diego!
Wake up!
-Fine.
-We have to fight back.
-Fine, be a killer.
-Now's the time!
Fine, go and kill them.
Let's all kill them!
How does that make us
any different from them?!
[tense music intensifies]
You're right, Diego.
Only another demon can finish them off.
-Jepoy.
Jepoy.
Jepoy, come on. You can't leave.
This isn't the right place for me anymore.
I don't know where to stand, Anna.
And where will you go?
Will you go to the Ardientes?
You're going to kill them all?
That's exactly what I'll do.
This is the only way, Anna.
I have to do this. I don't
want anyone else getting hurt.
No, Jepoy.
If you won't stay, I'm coming with you.
I won't let you hurt yourself.
Jepoy, do you understand me?
Don't leave, Jepoy.
Who knows what will happen to you?
[somber music playing]
Please don't go.
Ivy and I need you.
Do you understand me?
Thank you for everything, Anna.
Take care of yourself.
Take care of Ivy.
Always help her out.
-[Anna crying]
-Thank you, Anna.
Jepoy, please.
Jepoy!
Jepoy, please don't do this!
-Jepoy!
-You don't have to do this.
Don't.
[ominous music playing]
Madam, I've found her.
[ominous music intensifies]
Ma'am, ma'am.
Somebody wants to give you this.
Who?
Him.
[ominous music intensifies]
Please, don't. Don't!
Please, don't! Don't! Don't!
Don't [Emilia shouts]
Hurry. Get her inside.
[sinister music playing]
Who are you?!
What is this place?!
Why did you bring me here?!
Stop right there! I'm warning you.
The last guy who tried to take
advantage of me is dead now!
We won't do that to you.
Then, why did you bring me here?!
Are you one of Papa's men?!
Did he order you to kill me?!
Then, don't waste your time
and just kill me!
We're not going to kill you.
Then why did you bring me here?!
Who are you?!
Take a shower and clean yourself up.
Then, get changed.
Later, you'll have a visitor.
A visitor?
Let's go.
Wait! Who are you?!
Why did you bring me here?
Hey!
[slow tense music playing]
Atty. De Jesus?
Emilia, we've been
looking all over for you.
These guys kidnapped me.
I don't even know why I'm here.
Hold on, Attorney,
what are you doing here?
They abducted me and brought
me here to tell you the news.
Huh? What news?
Haven't you heard?
The judge already dismissed your case.
How did that happen?
Divine Oytengco
and Corazon Samartino are dead.
The prosecution cannot present
any more witnesses.
All the evidence against you
also disappeared.
Even the jailbreaking charges
against you have been dropped.
My charges got dropped?
Who helped me?
I don't know, Emilia.
Who ordered you to kidnap me?
Come on! Answer me!
You won't stay here long, Mrs. Torillo.
We'll take you to Poblacion
Ardiente as soon as possible.
I can't leave this place yet.
I still need a car and a phone.
[Ivy] What kind of nonsense is this?!
How could Emilia's case get dropped?
I'm sorry, Ivy, but they got everything.
All of our evidence
and documents are gone!
It's as if none of it existed.
Okay, fine! I get it!
But, who did it?!
Who else could've helped Emilia?!
It can't possibly be Julio.
He would never help Emilia
after she betrayed him.
If it's not Julio,
then Jaguar's probably behind this.
[tense music playing]
[raindrops pattering]
Thank you.
Jaguar.
Jaguar, thank you.
You know, I've been trying to call you,
but I cannot seem to contact you.
But finally, you're here.
Finally, I have the chance to talk to you.
I just want to thank you for saving me.
We had to move our headquarters.
What happened to you?
What? You mean to say
that you haven't heard about
what happened to me?
Jaguar, you saved me.
You're the one who cleared
all the evidence against me.
You even got rid of the witnesses
so I could be free.
I'm technically free
because of you, Jaguar.
I'm not the one who helped you, Emilia.
What?
You've got to be kidding me, right?
I wish I had, but I couldn't.
Okay.
If you weren't the one
who helped me, then who did?
It was Julio.
That's impossible, Jaguar!
My father already disowned me.
He said he no longer has a daughter.
So, my father couldn't possibly
have helped me!
He probably needs something from you.
If Julio helped you, I'm sure
he expects something in return.
That's why you have to gain his trust
and make sure he doesn't outwit you.
[heart rate monitor beeping]
Governor, Mr. Chen sent these.
Oh!
Well, please tell Mr. Chen,
thank you for his gift,
and I'm looking forward to
working with him some more in the future.
-Yes, Governor.
-Please put it there.
Okay. Please let my visitor in.
-Okay, Governor.
-Okay.
[Julio chuckles]
Oh, car keys.
[suspenseful music playing]
Money, money, money, money, money, money.
See, Arnaldo?
That is why we spend
millions during elections,
to make sure that we'll win.
So that we can make… more… millions.
You see? That's the point.
[Julio chuckles]
The reason why there should always be
an Ardiente holding a
position in the government…
is to ensure that
we continue raking in money.
But it seems like…
we have a problem right now.
Looks like we harbored a traitor
under our roof, and…
you know who that person is.
Does the name Ivy Aguas ring a bell?
Arnaldo, is this woman…
an enemy or not, huh?
Well, doesn't really matter, my son.
We're about to find out
that woman's true allegiance
and Grandpa Julio
will take care of everything.
Once I prove that she's betraying us,
I'll put a bullet in her head
and feed her to street rats.
[knocking on door]
-[tense music playing]
-Come in. Come in.
Governor.
Is this what they mean when they say:
"to the victor belongs the spoils"?
Something like that.
How are you, Ms. Aguas?
Yes.
So, why were you looking for me?
Well…
someone told me that Diego's group
is planning to cause trouble again,
and it seems like they just
don't know when to quit!
Okay. So, what do you plan
to do with them?
What does a father do
to his rebellious children?
Shouldn't he teach them a lesson?
This might be against my will,
but I need to do this.
And I choose you, Ms. Aguas,
to carry out their punishment.
[tense music playing]
So, go with the Colonel.
Take them. Capture them.
Talk to them.
Kidnap whoever you see in Diego's camp.
After that…
turn them into ash, okay?
Me?! Why me?
What use is the Colonel then?
Is he useless now?
What about your other men?
You want me to do it?
You know, Miss Aguas,
I chose you because I noticed that
when it comes to Diego's group…
you become weak.
I think I need to toughen you up.
I need to make sure you can still help me,
and that you're on my side.
Governor, what else do you want from me?
Tell me!
I risked my life for Arnaldo.
I provided a huge amount
of money to fund your campaign.
And yet, you're still suspicious of me.
What else can I do to prove my loyalty?
Well, that's easy.
Just do what I asked you to do.
Kill Diego's men.
[Ivy] No.
Well, you choose.
Either you kill them…
…or I kill you.
[tense music intensifies]
Four against one?
The odds aren't in your favor, Ms. Aguas.
I'm giving you a choice, Ms. Aguas.
Kill…
…or be killed.
Let go of your gun.
If you weren't a soulless,
cold-hearted person like me,
you wouldn't survive in my world.
Is that what you want me to do?
Eliminate all of Diego's men?
Something like that.
I want to see…
their blood on your hands.
Okay.
Fine.
If it will make you happy,
I'll do it.
But I want something in return.
Oh, tit for tat. Name it.
I want to be involved in all
of your business transactions,
legal or illegal.
I want a bigger piece of the pie.
[Julio chuckles]
Money and greed.
At the end of the day,
it still boils down to that.
Agreed.
[suspenseful music playing]
This is just the beginning
of Julio's vicious plans.
Many more will be affected and get hurt.
That's why I won't blame you if…
you want to back down.
I don't want any of you to get hurt,
so I'm letting you
return to your families.
Live a peaceful life,
a life free from fear.
But I promise that I'll continue
this fight, no matter what.
I won't give up.
That's a promise.
So, please go home. You too, Marlon.
We're not leaving you, Diego.
We're not afraid of Julio.
We'll fight with you until the end.
As long as you're with us,
we won't lose hope.
We'll fight for a new Ardiente!
[uplifting music playing]
Yes!
-We'll fight.
-We'll fight on.
We will fight.
-Right.
-We will fight.
Fight!
Fight on, son!
We'll fight on.
Fight!
-Fight.
-We will fight!
Fight!
Thank you, everyone.
[line ringing]
Oh, Ivy.
You are still here.
Are you surprised?
I'm no longer a corrupt queen.
I am the real queen,
and I am so back!
Well, welcome back, corruption queen!
You should've told me you were coming.
I would've hired a caterer…
-No need.
-…and a band.
Actually, I came here
to surprise everyone.
You're lucky I didn't catch you scheming.
Oh, come on, Emilia.
Me, scheming?
You've never caught me
because I'm innocent.
Let's be honest, in this household,
you're the one who's always
scheming behind people's backs.
So you told Papa on me?!
Don't you ever accuse me of something
you can't even prove.
Go on, Ivy! Keep lying!
I'm not stupid, you know.
But, let me just remind you, Ivy,
that I am so back here in this house.
This is my family, and this is my house,
and whether you like it or not,
I am going to stay here!
[Emilia chuckles]
Emilia.
Hi, Papa.
[tense music playing]
Boss Jaguar couldn't have gotten far.
He was shot.
He could be hiding around here.
What if he's dead?
We have to make sure.
Damian.
[henchman] Dude.
Did you guys hear that?
Someone said the boss' name.
[doorbell rings]
[knocking on gate]
Hello?
-[knocking on gate]
-Anyone home?
Hello.
-[knocking on gate]
-Anyone home?
What's going on?
Dude, I don't think he's in there.
But I heard someone say "Damian".
Is he the only person named Damian?
Come on.
Papa.
I came here because
I want to know the truth.
Are you the one who cleared my case?
What do you think?
Who do you think would help you?
You know, Emilia,
I wanted to make sure
I'd win in the election.
When I knew that,
I went to clear your case right away.
Thank you, Papa.
Does that mean you've forgiven me?
No matter what you did against me,
you're still my daughter, Emilia.
And as your father,
I am obligated to take care of you.
Emilia.
You are an Ardiente.
And that is one thing…
that will never change,
whether I like it or not.
Papa, thank you.
Thank you, Papa.
Thank you.
Papa, I promise you,
you're not going to regret
giving me a second chance.
I'm going to prove to you my worth.
I'm not going to betray you again.
I will cut my ties with Jaguar.
I promise you that, Papa.
I promise.
[Ivy] Go figure.
Like father, like daughter.
Those two are cut
from the same two-faced cloth.
[mouthing] Bravo.
Who were those men, Damian?
Why are you hiding from them?
Tell me the truth.
If I find out you still haven't
given up being a criminal,
I will personally bring you to jail,
just like what your brother did.
I'm not a criminal, Camia.
Those were the men who robbed me.
Why didn't you go to the police?
I don't want trouble.
You might get involved.
I just want a quiet life.
You don't want trouble, Damian?
Or are you hiding something from me?
Camia, believe me. I've changed.
I'm not a criminal anymore.
I live a completely different life now.
I have to admit,
I still don't completely
trust you, Damian.
But I'll give you a chance
to prove yourself.
But the moment I find out
that you're lying to us,
I will never forgive you.
[tense music playing]
-[oxygen machine running]
-[heart rate monitor beeping]
[Emilia crying]
How are you, my son?
Mommy's back.
[exhales sharply]
I missed you.
-[machine beeps]
-Arnaldo.
Do you think…
your grandfather really
helped me with my case?
If it wasn't your grandfather or Jaguar,
who else would want to be
involved in my life?
[cell phone ringing]
Hello, Attorney.
Have you done what I asked you to do?
Yes, Emilia.
I tracked down the owner of the
house those men brought you to.
I also did some research
on that car they let you use.
They're both registered
to one Mercedes Palacio.
Huh? Who is that?
It's an alias.
No one knows who this person is.
We're not even sure
if she's actually she or a he.
Plenty of men use female names
as their aliases
to confuse anybody probing
for their real identity.
So, Attorney, there is still a possibility
that my father helped me?
At this point,
anything is possible, Emilia.
[Julio] Sanggano.
I want you to have our people figure out
who fixed Emilia's case.
Governor, didn't you help Emilia?
I've already disowned
that daughter of mine.
I can't forgive her
for what she did to me.
I just let her believe
that I was responsible
for fixing her case.
But the truth is,
I just want to know who really did.
Because one day,
that person might be a threat to us.
Conduct a thorough investigation,
but make sure Emilia doesn't
find out what you're doing.
Jaguar's the only other person
who could help Emilia, right?
[chuckles]
Don't be so sure, Sanggano.
There's a lot you don't know about Emilia.
Yes, Governor.
[ominous music playing]
The two of you will investigate
Ma'am Emilia's acquittal.
I expect a report by tonight.
-Yes, sir.
-Go on.
You two, come with me.
We have another assignment.
-Yes, sir.
Ms. Ivy Aguas.
Where are you going?
-It's none of your business.
-Wait. You can't leave.
Governor's orders.
We're attacking Diego's group tonight.
[suspenseful music playing]
[Emilia] You're hiding
too many secrets, Papa.
I need to get close to you.
Really close.
To dig into your deepest
and darkest secrets.
And I have to get rid of your
favorite pet, Ivy, to get there.
What the hell are you doing here?
Hi, Papa.
I came here to…
make up for all my mistakes.
I was going to suggest something
if you're up to it.
-Hey.
-I'll do it.
Lift it up.
Okay.
-Take care.
-Yeah.
-Thanks.
-Take care, all of you.
-Bye.
-We have a long day tomorrow.
[Loring] Okay. Take care. Yeah. Oh, okay.
Let's talk tomorrow.
Oh! What's this?
-Hey, what's happening?!
-[tires screeching]
-Auntie! Auntie!
-What's happening?
-[gunshots]
-[woman screams]
[screaming]
What's this?
Where are you taking us?! Huh?!
Auntie Camia, stay here, okay?
Batch, look after her.
-Okay.
-Diego.
-Wait a minute!
-Auntie! Wait!
-Hurry up!
-Don't hurt us!
Auntie Camia, I'm going to help Diego.
[Loring] Wait! Pandoy!
Pandoy! Pandoy! Wait a minute!
-[gunshots]
-[Loring shouts]
Diego!
-Diego!
-[engine starts]
-Diego, help us!
-Anna, don't worry!
-[gunshots]
-[tires screeching]
Wait! Hey!
Auntie, those were our people.
Diego, I'm going to get help.
Diego, call my daughter.
She might know something!
This might be Julio's doing!
[line ringing]
[phone vibrates]
Aren't you going to answer that?
She's not picking up.
Come on. Let's go inside.
No.
What's it to you?
I don't have to answer
an unimportant call.
Let's go.
[car engine starts]
The judge who dismissed
Mrs. Emilia's case is missing.
And no one knows if he was paid to do it,
or who paid him.
We also can't find the one
who took all the evidence.
I'm sorry, Governor.
We did everything we could
to find whoever helped Ma'am Emilia.
But everyone we asked
seemed scared to talk about her.
Whoever it is,
they can't hide from me forever.
Call Colonel Sanggano.
I need to talk to him
about Ivy Aguas' mission.
Yes, Governor.
[tense music playing]
Go inside!
-What's happening?
-Auntie Loring!
-Please spare us!
-Hurry!
-What gives?!
-Move!
-Have mercy!
-Please, have mercy!
What will you do to us?
All of you!
-Shut up!
-Be quiet.
Especially you two.
Okay, tie them all up.
-[cell phone ringing]
-Please, have mercy.
Hurry!
-Help!
-Have mercy, sir.
[Jose] Yes, Governor?
Okay, Governor.
Wait for the others. They're on their way.
Make sure no one escapes.
Yes, Boss.
The governor wants me to take you home.
Why? What are we going to do
with the hostages?
Are we leaving them here?
What are you planning to do?
Just follow me.
The governor changed his plan.
Then, tell me what the new plan is.
[sighs] It doesn't involve you,
Ms. Aguas. Let's go.
-Colonel, hey!
-Let's go.
-[clamoring]
-What did we do to you?
-Silence!
-Shut up!
-We didn't do anything.
-Hey!
-Why are you doing this to us?!
-We didn't do anything wrong!
-Please let us go!
We didn't do anything wrong!
-Hey! Come back here!
-Somebody, help us!
Stop moving around! Someone, help us!
Governor, you have a visitor.
It's Diego Torillo.
Let him in.
Oh…
Diego.
What are you doing here?
Didn't we teach you decency and
courtesy when you were younger?
Where did you take my supporters?
What did you do to them?
Who's "them"?
I don't know who the hell
you're talking about.
Stop acting innocent, Governor.
I'm the one you want to hurt, right?
So, take me and release my supporters.
Why do you always blame me
whenever something bad
happens to your supporters?
Why don't you ask
Ms. Ivy Aguas for a change?
Because from what I heard,
she was the one who
had your people abducted.
What?
Surprised?
Why don't you call her?
I know you have her number.
Have you two been talking
more often recently?
I don't have time to joke around with you.
And whatever your plan is,
I'll make sure you won't succeed.
Make sure…
Diego won't get in the way of my plans.
Yes, sir.
You can't leave until
the Governor says so.
Understand?
Tell the Governor he can't
just order me around.
I'm not afraid of him.
Don't disobey him
if you don't want any trouble.
[engine starts]
[phone ringing]
Hello.
[Julio] All right.
Follow her.
[engine starts]
[suspenseful music playing]
Auntie.
Diego, what did Julio say?
He said that Ivy's behind the kidnapping.
-Huh?
-I've been trying to call her…
…but I can't reach her.
The subscriber cannot be reached.
Auntie, I have a bad feeling about this.
Julio seems to know something about Ivy.
My goodness.
-Hey!
-Help us!
-Have mercy on us!
[tense music playing]
You, take that side. You, go there.
[phone ringing]
It's Ivy.
-Hello, Ivy?
-[Ivy] Diego.
Diego, Julio's men abducted
Anna and your supporters.
They're going to kill them!
Where did they take them?
To San Narciso.
Get there as soon as you can!
I'm on my way!
-Light it up?
-Go.
-Go, go. Set it on fire.
-Quickly. Come on!
-Hey!
-Help!
-Help us!
-Wait!
Help us!
Help!
-You bastards!
-Help! Help! Help us!
-Someone help!
-Help us!
Help! Help!
Please help us!
[crying]
[all] Help us! Please, help us!
[all coughing]
[Loring shouts]
Loring, stay strong.
Help!
-[people coughing]
-Help!
Cheers, Dante.
You're unbelievable.
You actually went back
to try and get me out.
You know…
you've always been the better man.
You were always the good guy,
the smart one.
You even won the heart
of the woman we both love!
It was always you!
You had everything.
I give up, Dante.
You're the winner.
[melancholic music playing]
I give up!
I'm tired of living like this!
Whether or not you believe me,
I longed to live a life like yours!
But no one would give me the opportunity!
No one but Camia.
She alone gave me the chance
to turn over a new leaf!
[tense music playing]
-Help!
-Somebody help us!
[Loring coughs]
-Someone, help us!
-Ivy?!
Wait!
Ivy, we're trapped inside!
Please help us!
-Ivy!
-Please help us!
[loud clattering]
Help!
[clattering]
Ivy!
-Ivy! Save us.
-Pandoy!
[tense music playing]
-[Loring groans]
-[Anna coughs]
-Come on!
-Go ahead.
-Get out of here!
-Thank you!
[Loring coughs]
[Anna coughs]
[people coughing]
You guys go ahead! Come on.
Let's get out of here.
[indistinct chatter, coughing]
Let's go.
[people continue coughing]
Go on.
Hey.
Go on! Get out of here!
Get in the jeepney!
-Ivy! Wait, what about you?
-I can take care of myself.
Go now before Julio's men see you.
The Ardientes might catch you.
No, they won't. Go!
Get on that jeepney and call Diego.
-[jeepney engine starts]
-Take care.
Get out of here.
Ivy.
[Emilia laughs]
How are you, my treacherous friend?
You seem to look okay.
And, finally, I caught you red-handed.
I now have evidence, so, it's obvious.
You can't lie to me anymore.
Traitor!
[suspenseful music playing]
[Diego] Ivy Aguas is on our side.
She's the reason why
we should keep fighting!
[Julio] I've caught you now.
We set the trap,
and you jumped right into it.
You're a traitor.
And we were right all along.
I won't let any traitors
walk out of here alive.
[Ivy] I'm not done yet, old man!
If Lily was safe,
she would've called by now.
-You think you're tough, huh?
-What are you doing?
[Emilia laughing]
[theme music playing]